[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "How many countries are there in Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 54
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "How many regions are there in Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 6
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Name all the geographic regions of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Southern", "Northern", "Sahel", "Eastern", "Western", "Central"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Northern region of Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Northern region of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Algeria", "Egypt", "Libya", "Morocco", "Tunisia"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Central region of Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 8
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Central region of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Angola", "Central African Republic (CAR)", "Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC)", "Republic of the Congo (Congo)", "Equatorial Guinea", "Gabon", "Sao Tome and Principe", "South Sudan"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Western region of Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 14
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Western region of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Benin", "Burkina Faso", "Cabo Verde", "Cameroon", "Cote d'Ivoire", "Gambia", "Ghana", "Guinea", "Guinea-Bissau", "Liberia", "Nigeria", "Senegal", "Sierra Leone", "Togo"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Southern region of Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 9
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Southern region of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Botswana", "Eswatini (formerly Swaziland)", "Lesotho", "Malawi", "Mozambique", "Namibia", "South Africa", "Zambia", "Zimbabwe"]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Eastern region of Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 13
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Eastern region of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Burundi", "Comoros", "Djibouti", "Eritrea", "Ethiopia", "Kenya", "Madagascar", "Mauritius", "Rwanda", "Seychelles", "Somalia", "Tanzania", "Uganda"]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Sahel region of Africa?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Sahel region of Africa",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Chad", "Mali", "Mauritania", "Niger", "Sudan"]
  },



  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "How many geographic Regions are there in Europe",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Name all the geographic Regions of Europe",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Northern", "Southern", "Eastern", "Western"]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Northern region of Europe?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Northern region of Europe",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Denmark", "Estonia", "Finland", "Iceland", "Ireland", "Latvia", "Lithuania", "Norway", "Sweden", "United Kingdom (UK)"]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Southern region of Europe?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 16
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Southern region of Europe",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Albania", "Andorra", "Bosnia and Herzegovina", "Croatia", "Greece", "Holy See", "Italy", "Macedonia", "Malta", "Monaco", "Montenegro", "Portugal", "San Marino", "Serbia", "Slovenia", "Spain"]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Eastern region of Europe?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Eastern region of Europe",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Belarus", "Bulgaria", "Czech Republic", "Hungary", "Moldova", "Poland", "Romania", "Russia", "Slovakia", "Ukraine"]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Western region of Europe?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 8
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Western region of Europe",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Austria", "Belgium", "France", "Germany", "Liechtenstein", "Luxembourg", "Netherlands", "Switzerland"]
  },




  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "How many geographic Regions are there in Asia",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 6
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Name all the geographic Regions of Asia",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Northern", "Southern", "Eastern", "Western", "Central", "South-East"]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "How many asian countries are in the Northern region of Asia?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Southern region of Asia?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 9
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Southern region of Asia",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Afghanistan", "Bangladesh", "Bhutan", "India", "Iran", "Maldives", "Nepal", "Pakistan", "Sri Lanka"]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Western region of Asia?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 18
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Western region of Asia",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Armenia", "Azerbaijan", "Bahrain", "Cyprus", "Georgia", "Iraq", "Israel", "Jordan", "Kuwait", "Lebanon", "Oman", "Palestine", "Qatar", "Saudi Arabia", "Syria", "Turkey", "United Arab Emirates (UAE)", "Yemen"]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "How many countries are in the South-East region of Asia?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 11
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the South-East region of Asia",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Brunei", "Cambodia", "Indonesia", "Laos", "Malaysia", "Myanmar (formerly Burma)", "Philippines", "Singapore", "Thailand", "Timor-Leste", "Vietnam"]
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Eastern region of Asia?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Eastern region of Asia",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["China", "Japan", "Mongolia", "North Korea", "South Korea"] 
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "How many countries are in the Central region of Asia?",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 5
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the Central region of Asia",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Kazakhstan", "Kyrgyzstan", "Tajikistan", "Turkmenistan", "Uzbekistan"]
  },






  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "How many countries are there in South America",
    "type": "single",
    "correctAnswer": 12
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "Name all the countries in the South America",
    "type": "multiple",
    "correctAnswer": ["Argentina", "Bolivia", "Brazil", "Chile", "Colombia", "Ecuador", "Guyana", "Paraguay", "Peru", "Suriname", "Uruguay", "Venezuela"]
  }







]